Associated Press, Washington, D.C., Bureau, News Dispatches
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Associated Press, Washington, D.C., Bureau, News Dispatches 1915-1930
MSS50666
Associated Press. Washington D.C. Bureau
375 items 254 containers 101.6 linear feet
Manuscript Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of news dispatches from the Washington, D.C., Bureau of the Associated Press containing an unbroken chronology of world and national events as reported by the news agency.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
Organizations
Associated Press. Washington D.C. Bureau.
Subjects
History, Modern--20th century.; News agencies.; News dispatches.
Places
United States--History--20th century.
Administrative Information
Provenance
The news dispatches of the Associated Press, Washington, D.C., Bureau, were given to the Library of Congress by the bureau in 1944. The collection was transferred from the Rare Book and Special Collections Division to the Manuscript Division in 1973.
Access and Restrictions
The news dispatches of the Associated Press, Washington, D.C., Bureau, are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of news dispatches of the Washington, D.C., Bureau of the Associated Press spans the period 1915-1930 and contain an unbroken chronology of world and national events as reported by the news agency.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged chronologically.
http://lccn.loc.gov/mm82050666
Container List
- 1915 (Box 1)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 2)
  - Mar.-Apr. (Box 3)
  - May (Box 4)
  - June (Box 5)
  - July (Box 6)
  - Aug. (Box 7)
  - Sept. (Box 8)
  - Oct. (Box 9)
  - Nov. (Box 10)
  - Dec. (Box 11)
- 1916 (Box 12)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. 1-13 (Box 13)
    - 14-29 (Box 14)
  - Mar. (Box 15)
    - 1-15
    - 15-31 (Box 16)
  - Apr. (Box 17)
  - May (Box 18)
  - June (Box 19)
  - July (Box 20)
  - Aug. (Box 21)
  - Sept. (Box 22)
  - Nov. (Box 23)
  - Dec. (Box 24)
- 1917 (Box 25)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 26)
  - Mar. (Box 27)
  - Apr. (Box 28)
  - May (Box 29)
  - June (Box 30)
  - July (Box 31)
  - Aug. (Box 32)
  - Sept. (Box 33)
  - Oct. (Box 34)
  - Nov. (Box 35)
  - Dec. (Box 36)
- 1918 (Box 37)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 38)
  - Mar. (Box 39)
  - Apr. (Box 40)
  - May (Box 41)
  - June (Box 42)
  - July (Box 43)
  - July (Box 44)
  - Aug. (Box 45)
  - Aug. (Box 46)
  - Sept. (Box 47)
  - Sept. (Box 48)
  - Oct. (Box 49)
  - Nov.-Dec. (Box 50)
  - Dec. (Box 51)
- 1919 (Box 52)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 53)
  - Mar.-Apr. (Box 54)
  - Apr.-May (Box 55)
  - June (Box 56)
  - July (Box 57)
  - Aug. (Box 58)
  - Sept. (Box 59)
  - Oct. (Box 60)
  - Nov. (Box 61)
  - Dec. (Box 62)
- 1920 (Box 63)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 64)
  - Mar.-Apr. (Box 65)
  - Apr.-May (Box 66)
  - May-June (Box 67)
  - July-Aug. (Box 68)
  - Sept.-Oct. (Box 69)
  - Nov.-Dec. (Box 70)
- 1921 (Box 71)
  - Jan.-Feb.
  - Feb.-Mar. (Box 72)
  - Apr.-May (Box 73)
  - May-June (Box 74)
  - July-Aug. (Box 75)
  - Sept.-Oct. (Box 76)
  - Oct.-Nov. (Box 77)
  - Nov. (Box 78)
  - Dec. (Box 79)
  - Dec. (Box 80)
- 1922 (Box 81)
  - Jan.
  - Jan. (Box 82)
  - Feb. (Box 83)
  - Mar. (Box 84)
  - Apr. (Box 85)
  - May (Box 86)
  - June (Box 87)
  - July (Box 88)
  - Aug.-Sept. (Box 89)
  - Sept.-Oct. (Box 90)
  - Nov.-Dec. (Box 91)
  - Dec. (Box 92)
- 1923 (Box 93)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 94)
  - Mar.-Apr. (Box 95)
  - Apr.-May (Box 96)
  - June-July (Box 97)
  - Aug.-Sept. (Box 98)
  - Oct.-Nov. (Box 99)
  - Dec. (Box 100)
- 1924 (Box 101)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 102)
  - Mar. (Box 103)
  - Apr. (Box 104)
  - Apr. (Box 105)
  - May (Box 106)
  - May-June (Box 107)
  - July-Aug. (Box 108)
  - Sept.-Oct. (Box 109)
  - Nov. (Box 110)
  - Dec. (Box 111)
- 1925 (Box 112)
  - Jan.
  - Feb.-Mar. (Box 113)
  - Mar.-Apr. (Box 114)
  - Apr.-May (Box 115)
  - June-July (Box 116)
  - Aug.-Sept. (Box 117)
  - Sept. (Box 118)
  - Oct. (Box 119)
  - Nov. (Box 120)
  - Nov. (Box 121)
  - Dec. (Box 122)
  - Dec. (Box 123)
- 1926 (Box 124)
  - Jan.
  - Feb. (Box 125)
  - Mar. (Box 126)
  - Mar. (Box 127)
  - Apr. (Box 128)
  - May (Box 129)
  - June (Box 130)
  - July (Box 131)
  - July (Box 132)
  - Aug.-Sept. (Box 133)
  - Oct.-Nov. (Box 134)
  - Nov. (Box 135)
  - Dec. (Box 136)
  - Dec. (Box 137)
- 1927 (Box 138)
  - Jan.
  - Jan. (Box 139)
  - Feb. (Box 140)
  - Feb. (Box 141)
  - Mar. (Box 142)
  - Mar. (Box 143)
  - Apr. (Box 144)
  - Apr. (Box 145)
  - May (Box 146)
  - May (Box 147)
  - June (Box 148)
  - June (Box 149)
  - July (Box 150)
  - July (Box 151)
  - Aug. (Box 152)
  - Aug. (Box 153)
  - Sept. (Box 154)
  - Sept. (Box 155)
  - Oct. (Box 156)
  - Oct. (Box 157)
  - Nov. (Box 158)
  - Nov. (Box 159)
  - Dec. (Box 160)
  - Dec. (Box 161)
- 1928 (Box 162)
  - Jan.
  - Jan. (Box 163)
  - Jan. (Box 164)
  - Feb. (Box 165)
  - Feb. (Box 166)
  - Mar. (Box 167)
  - Mar. (Box 168)
  - Mar. (Box 169)
  - Apr. (Box 170)
  - Apr. (Box 171)
  - Apr. (Box 172)
  - May (Box 173)
  - May (Box 174)
  - May (Box 175)
  - June (Box 176)
  - July (Box 177)
  - Aug. (Box 178)
  - Aug. (Box 179)
  - Sept. (Box 180)
  - Sept. (Box 181)
  - Oct. (Box 182)
  - Oct. (Box 183)
  - Nov. (Box 184)
  - Nov. (Box 185)
  - Nov.-Dec. (Box 186)
  - Dec. (Box 187)
  - Dec. (Box 188)
- 1929 (Box 189)
  - Jan.
  - Jan. (Box 190)
  - Jan. (Box 191)
  - Feb. (Box 192)
  - Feb. (Box 193)
  - Feb. (Box 194)
  - Mar. (Box 195)
  - Mar. (Box 196)
  - Mar. (Box 197)
  - Apr. (Box 198)
  - Apr. (Box 199)
  - Apr. (Box 200)
  - May (Box 201)
  - May (Box 202)
  - May (Box 203)
  - June (Box 204)
  - June (Box 205)
  - June (Box 206)
  - July (Box 207)
  - Aug. (Box 208)
  - Aug. (Box 209)
  - Aug. (Box 210)
  - Sept. (Box 211)
  - Sept. (Box 212)
  - Sept. (Box 213)
  - Oct. (Box 214)
  - Oct. (Box 215)
  - Oct. (Box 216)
  - Nov. (Box 217)
  - Nov. (Box 218)
  - Nov. (Box 219)
  - Dec. (Box 220)
  - Dec. (Box 221)
  - Dec. (Box 222)
- 1930 (Box 223)
  - Jan.
  - Jan. (Box 224)
  - Jan. (Box 225)
  - Feb. (Box 226)
  - Feb. (Box 227)
  - Feb. (Box 228)
  - Mar. (Box 229)
  - Mar. (Box 230)
  - Mar. (Box 231)
  - Apr. (Box 232)
  - Apr. (Box 233)
  - Apr. (Box 234)
  - May (Box 235)
  - May (Box 236)
  - May (Box 237)
  - June (Box 238)
  - June (Box 239)
  - June (Box 240)
  - July (Box 241)
  - July (Box 242)
  - July (Box 243)
  - Aug. (Box 244)
  - Aug. (Box 245)
  - Aug. (Box 246)
  - Sept. (Box 247)
  - Sept. (Box 248)
  - Sept. (Box 249)
  - Oct. (Box 250)
  - Oct. (Box 251)
  - Oct. (Box 252)
  - Nov. (Box 253)
  - Nov. (Box 254)